sunglasswarehouse.com 2007-07-07

# Privacy Policy | SunglassWarehouse.com

The Site ("sunglasswarehouse.com") is owned and operated by One Click Internet Ventures, LLC. We have created this privacy policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting your personal information and informing you about how we handle it. You have our promise that we will not electronically process your personal information in any way that is incompatible with this Policy. Each time you visit the Site or provide us with information, by doing so you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy at that time. 

**Hosted by Yahoo! Store**  
This site is hosted by Yahoo! Store. Yahoo! hosts the store pages, ordering system, and order data. Yahoo! automatically collects order information but may only use this information in the aggregate. If you accessed this store through Yahoo! Shopping, Yahoo! also automatically collects information about your shopping experience. Please see the [Yahoo! Privacy Policy](http://privacy.yahoo.com/privacy/us/) for more information about how Yahoo! uses this information. 

**Collection of Data**  
This Site does not collect identity or contact information from Internet Users to this website. This site may however, collect non-personally identifiable information, for example, browser type, operating system, domain name, time spent on the web site, or referring link. This information may be used for system, website, and process improvements. 

This site does not sell or rent personally identifying information. This site does not disclose personally identifying information to anyone that is not authorized to do so. This site uses anonymous user data to create and report the browsing, purchasing and/or lead form completion activities of anonymous users. This site reserves the right to release information on Internet Users if compelled to do so by proper judicial or governmental authorities. Disclosure shall be limited to only to those we are compelled to disclose to. At present, all information processing occurs in the United States. 

This Site uses cookies to keep track of session IDs. A cookie is a small piece of information stored by a web server on your computer's hard drive. Any cookie in use by our server is temporary and will be removed when the user logs out or is timed-out by the server. Additionally, we record IP addresses to analyze trends and administer the site. An IP address is a number that is automatically assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider when you connect to the Internet. IP addresses are NOT linked to any personally identifiable information. 

**Information Other Websites Collect From You**  
On the Site, we place links to other Websites operated by other parties. Some of these other Websites contain our brand names and trademarks and other intellectual property that we own; others do not. When you click on these links and visit these other Websites, regardless of whether or not they contain our brand names, trademarks and other intellectual property, you need to be aware that we do not control these other Websites or these other Websites' business practices, and that this privacy policy does not apply to these other Websites. Consequently, the operators of these other Websites may collect different kinds of information about you, and may use and disclose that information in different ways than we would if it were collected on the Site. We encourage you to review their privacy policies and remind you that we will not be responsible for their actions.

**Updating this Policy**  
We will revise or update this Policy as it deems appropriate, including for example, if our practices change, as we change existing or add new services, as we develop better ways to inform you of products we think will be of interest, or if the law so requires. You should refer back to this page often for the latest information and the effective date of any changes. 

**Contact Us**  
We are committed to the policies set forth in this Policy. If you have any questions, comments or concerns about this Policy, please contact [info@sunglasswarehouse.com](mailto:info@sunglasswarehouse.com).
